I would like to show you a couple of examples real quick of a good corner and a bad corner.
A good corner would be when the two edges meet and they line up and they are nice and straight and flush.
This right here would be an example of a good corner.
Now I'm going to demonstrate to you what a bad corner would look like.
This right here would be a bad corner and the reason it would be a bad corner is because both drywalls from both sides of here do not meet up straight inside here and since it did that there is no meat for this to grab on to right here and it just makes it harder for it to set in place.
Now as long as it is straight which is it, when we installed it we made sure that the corner bead did go on straight.
It is still alright.
Although it would be better if the drywall ran underneath this.
Now the reason this happened is probably a sheet was cut and put into place and it was just accidentally cut wrong which happens.
So we try to avoid that.
It is kind of like screwing your screw in too far.
We really try to avoid that and we try and get all our corners perfect but once in a while when one does happen, if we can still make it look perfect and it will work out then sometimes we just go ahead with it.